[{"answer": "Every day.", "docId": "111016pmt", "aSentId": 24, "question": "Do you ever sit here, just the three of you sometimes, and think, how did we get here?", "qSentId": 23}, {"answer": "You know, I had the occasion to go back to the house I grew up in Ashton, Birmingham a few months ago.", "docId": "111016pmt", "aSentId": 31, "question": "I mean, I just wonder whether sometimes you have that moment where you just think how did this happen?", "qSentId": 30}, {"answer": "I was kind of one up from Ozzy because we had inside bathrooms in our house.", "docId": "111016pmt", "aSentId": 39, "question": "Sharon, how did you do it?", "qSentId": 38}, {"answer": "Absolutely, yes, because -- I mean, I wouldn't be here talking to you.", "docId": "111016pmt", "aSentId": 63, "question": "If you had your time again, would you choose to be in that MTV show?", "qSentId": 62}, {"answer": "It's a very difficult question for me to answer because I did -- it became huger than I ever expected it to be.", "docId": "111016pmt", "aSentId": 79, "question": "If you had the choice now to make that series or not?", "qSentId": 78}, {"answer": "Well, I'm lucky.", "docId": "111016pmt", "aSentId": 99, "question": "And what do you think of that, coming from Britain and going back there and seeing it's so much more prevalent now, given what it did to you and your life and the impact on your family?", "qSentId": 98}, {"answer": "Lucky is not the word.", "docId": "111016pmt", "aSentId": 111, "question": "Do you feel lucky that none of your kids ended up like Amy Winehouse?", "qSentId": 110}, {"answer": "I think she said -- she's including you as one of the children, Ozzy.", "docId": "111016pmt", "aSentId": 120, "question": "What about you?", "qSentId": 119}, {"answer": "But then at the same time, it has nothing to do with the size, the age, the width, (INAUDIBLE), it's to do with the look.", "docId": "111016pmt", "aSentId": 130, "question": "How do they think their bodies can continue doing this, and doing this?", "qSentId": 129}, {"answer": "A lot.", "docId": "111016pmt", "aSentId": 137, "question": "People you've known?", "qSentId": 136}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111016pmt", "aSentId": 145, "question": "What do you feel?", "qSentId": 144}, {"answer": "It's only now, it's only after the fact, my folks never said, you know, I didn't think about anything.", "docId": "111016pmt", "aSentId": 157, "question": "When you watched her talking about that, Ozzy, what did you feel?", "qSentId": 156}, {"answer": "I don't know, because I can't remember.", "docId": "111016pmt", "aSentId": 188, "question": "I mean, that's an extraordinary moment to reach, isn't it?", "qSentId": 187}, {"answer": "It was -- it was pretty damn scary because, you know, you're in a house, no neighbors each side, your kids are asleep.", "docId": "111016pmt", "aSentId": 204, "question": "Well, in a funny way, in the movie -- in the movie, it was a bit surreal watching that because, Sharon was able to kind of deal with it in a relatively calm way when in fact it must have been at the time just grotesque, wasn't it?", "qSentId": 203}, {"answer": "Oh, God, yes.", "docId": "111016pmt", "aSentId": 211, "question": "What was the answer when you ask yourself that?", "qSentId": 210}, {"answer": "No, as harder -- as hard as Ozzy would hit me, I would clobber him back.", "docId": "111016pmt", "aSentId": 223, "question": "How would you imagine that you're a shrinking violet in any relationship, Sharon?", "qSentId": 222}, {"answer": "Honestly, it's just kind of --", "docId": "111016pmt", "aSentId": 228, "question": "What do you feel when you hear that?", "qSentId": 227}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "111016pmt", "aSentId": 243, "question": "Never in front of the kids?", "qSentId": 242}, {"answer": "You never hit a girl.", "docId": "111016pmt", "aSentId": 246, "question": "What?", "qSentId": 245}, {"answer": "Yes, that's exactly right.", "docId": "111016pmt", "aSentId": 251, "question": "So what about you (EXPLETIVE DELETED) hitting us then?", "qSentId": 250}, {"answer": "Well, yes.", "docId": "111016pmt", "aSentId": 256, "question": "But do you feel, Ozzy, you're a completely different human being now?", "qSentId": 255}, {"answer": "It was great fun until it wasn't.", "docId": "111016pmt", "aSentId": 263, "question": "And to put the flipside on it, was it for a long time great fun being Ozzy Osbourne?", "qSentId": 262}, {"answer": "I don't know.", "docId": "111016pmt", "aSentId": 270, "question": "Enough of this?", "qSentId": 269}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "111016pmt", "aSentId": 288, "question": "Sharon, would you go along with that?", "qSentId": 287}, {"answer": "And Jack just cracked up.", "docId": "111016pmt", "aSentId": 298, "question": "Had you pissed on me as well?", "qSentId": 297}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "111016pmt", "aSentId": 303, "question": "You don't agree, Ozzy?", "qSentId": 302}, {"answer": "Maybe was.", "docId": "111016pmt", "aSentId": 311, "question": "It wasn't Jack reacting to you?", "qSentId": 310}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111016pmt", "aSentId": 316, "question": "Jack, do you remember the incident your mom is talking about?", "qSentId": 315}, {"answer": "Nothing.", "docId": "111016pmt", "aSentId": 346, "question": "What have you got against bats?", "qSentId": 345}, {"answer": "I did some have crazy stuff when I was out there, you know.", "docId": "111016pmt", "aSentId": 348, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 347}, {"answer": "My mom's a very strong-willed woman.", "docId": "111016pmt", "aSentId": 368, "question": "Am I misreading the tea leaves?", "qSentId": 367}, {"answer": "Without a doubt.", "docId": "111016pmt", "aSentId": 373, "question": "Is that understood?", "qSentId": 372}, {"answer": "The whole thing was --", "docId": "111016pmt", "aSentId": 382, "question": "Even now, though?", "qSentId": 381}, {"answer": "Dad likes to slam things.", "docId": "111016pmt", "aSentId": 386, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 385}, {"answer": "Not really.", "docId": "111016pmt", "aSentId": 390, "question": "Ozzy, would you say you have anger management issues?", "qSentId": 389}, {"answer": "It was the strangest thing because we were all on such a big high from the show being such a success.", "docId": "111016pmt", "aSentId": 403, "question": "What was that like, do you think, in reality for the family?", "qSentId": 402}, {"answer": "They were very respectful.", "docId": "111016pmt", "aSentId": 425, "question": "Why are we living our lives in this crazy soap opera when it's so serious?", "qSentId": 424}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "111016pmt", "aSentId": 437, "question": "Did you think Ozzy could have coped if you had died?", "qSentId": 436}, {"answer": "No one really told me the severity of it.", "docId": "111016pmt", "aSentId": 466, "question": "Jack, what was it like for you?", "qSentId": 465}, {"answer": "I wanted to get out.", "docId": "111016pmt", "aSentId": 482, "question": "What were you thinking, Ozzy, as you were lying in hospital?", "qSentId": 481}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "111016pmt", "aSentId": 496, "question": "Never boring, is it?", "qSentId": 495}, {"answer": "On his death bed, this is what he -- on his death bed, he said to me -- the only thing I have to say to you -- he thought all drugs were speed or sleeping pills.", "docId": "111016pmt", "aSentId": 522, "question": "How did he feel about the way you were enjoying all that fame?", "qSentId": 521}, {"answer": "I know he would.", "docId": "111016pmt", "aSentId": 530, "question": "Do you think he would have been very proud of you, of what you've now done with your life?", "qSentId": 529}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111016pmt", "aSentId": 535, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 534}, {"answer": "Sharon, you had very much more complicated relationship with your father.", "docId": "111016pmt", "aSentId": 537, "question": "I mean, he was a nice guy in his own way, you know?", "qSentId": 536}, {"answer": "I got the most amazing gifts from my father, the gift of music.", "docId": "111016pmt", "aSentId": 542, "question": "When that happened, what was your real emotion when you realized he was no longer going to be any part of your life?", "qSentId": 541}, {"answer": "I was pissed.", "docId": "111016pmt", "aSentId": 565, "question": "Horrified?", "qSentId": 564}, {"answer": "I'd been drinking big time.", "docId": "111016pmt", "aSentId": 567, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 566}, {"answer": "I don't know.", "docId": "111016pmt", "aSentId": 569, "question": "What did you think when you heard it?", "qSentId": 568}, {"answer": "All I could think of was, because as usual, as soon as Ozzy and I get down to a table, we're throwing in the food, and he had a big pat of butter on his crotch.", "docId": "111016pmt", "aSentId": 573, "question": "What did I think?", "qSentId": 572}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "111016pmt", "aSentId": 592, "question": "Do you care much?", "qSentId": 591}, {"answer": "It is an almost impossible job these days because the news cycle is so relentless, that people just get bored with the president very quickly, (INAUDIBLE), how it's a better story.", "docId": "111016pmt", "aSentId": 597, "question": "I don't understand it, you know?", "qSentId": 596}, {"answer": "I don't know.", "docId": "111016pmt", "aSentId": 599, "question": "What do you think, Sharon?", "qSentId": 598}, {"answer": "I think he's an incredible man.", "docId": "111016pmt", "aSentId": 608, "question": "Do you think President Obama is still too young?", "qSentId": 607}, {"answer": "I just like it.", "docId": "111016pmt", "aSentId": 613, "question": "What do you think of America?", "qSentId": 612}, {"answer": "It wouldn't surprise me.", "docId": "111016pmt", "aSentId": 643, "question": "Did you ever imagine, Jack, your father would become a sort of medical advisory board?", "qSentId": 642}, {"answer": "I haven't got a clue.", "docId": "111016pmt", "aSentId": 658, "question": "How did it keep going?", "qSentId": 657}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111016pmt", "aSentId": 674, "question": "Do you feel like all the torment has been worth it?", "qSentId": 673}, {"answer": "You know, I was meant to be with Sharon and Sharon was meant to be with me.", "docId": "111016pmt", "aSentId": 677, "question": "We're so lucky, you know?", "qSentId": 676}, {"answer": "Oh, yes.", "docId": "111016pmt", "aSentId": 682, "question": "Jack?", "qSentId": 681}, {"answer": "Jack is a lone voice of sanity.", "docId": "111016pmt", "aSentId": 685, "question": "Where did we find little Jack?", "qSentId": 684}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111016pmt", "aSentId": 697, "question": "Is that right?", "qSentId": 696}, {"answer": "I'm excited.", "docId": "111016pmt", "aSentId": 702, "question": "How do you feel?", "qSentId": 701}, {"answer": "I'm in shock.", "docId": "111016pmt", "aSentId": 707, "question": "Ozzy, how are you feeling about this?", "qSentId": 706}, {"answer": "I think it is fabulous.", "docId": "111016pmt", "aSentId": 709, "question": "Good shock?", "qSentId": 708}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "111016pmt", "aSentId": 718, "question": "You are not a grandma, right?", "qSentId": 717}]